http://www.datasrc.net/privacy-policy/

Your Enterprise Resource Planning and Customer Relationship Management Experts
508-852-8585
HomeProductsMicrosoft Dynamics GPBusiness IntelligenceFinancialsManufacturingSupply ChainHR & PayrollToolsProject ManagementMicrosoft Dynamics CRMPassport Business SolutionsMicrosoft ForecasterMicrosoft SQL ServerSharepointSecurity ProductsESETSymantecMcAfeeMicrosoft Office 365IT ServicesProduct Related IT ServicesCustomizationsImplementationsIntegrationsUpgradesManaged ServicesIT ServicesAssessments / AuditsNetwork DesignWireless NetworkingVirtualizationMigrations & UpgradesSecurity / Compliance AuditsDisaster Recovery & BackupManaged ServicesIndustriesDistribution & Supply ChainFinancial ServicesNon-Profit /
Public SectorProfessional ServicesSupport & TrainingSupportTrainingAbout UsWhy choose DSi?Career OpportunitiesLocation / Contact infoGP Customer BlogDynamics GP Daily BlogUser PreferenceWhat Table is the Field Stored In?Extender FieldsWhat does this field do?SmartList Run FasterGreat New GP2013 FeatureSelecting A Printer in GP2013Purchase Order PrepaymentGP2013 Reprint Check/Remittance InformationCRM/GP Integrating Accounts
Home > Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyWhat information do we collect? We collect information from you when you register on our site, respond to a survey or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.What do we use your information for? Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: To personalize your experience(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)To improve our website(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
To improve customer service(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
To send periodic emails
The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails and/or any further electronic information, please send a removal request e-mail to sales@datasrc.net. How do we protect your information? We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. Do we use cookies? Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain informationWe use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.Do we disclose any information to outside parties? We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third party links Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.California Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceBecause we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.Online Privacy Policy Only This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Your Consent By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy Policy If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Contacting Us If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 3-15 East Mountain StreetWorcester, ma 01606USAsales@datasrc.net508-852-8563
Contact Us
Name											*
Email Address											*
Phone Number											*
Please type the letters and numbers shown in the image
Please type the letters and numbers shown in the image.
HOMEMICROSOFT SOLUTIONS Microsoft  Dynamics GP PremiseMicrosoft Dynamics CRM PremiseMicrosoft ForecasterMicrosoft SQL ServerMicrosoft SharePoint ALTERNATIVE ERP PRODUCTSPassport Business Solutions SECURITY PRODUCTSESETMcAfeeSymantec
IT SERVICES IT Assessments & Audits IT Security Assessments & Compliancy AuditsBusiness Needs AssessmentMicrosoft Dynamics ImplementationsMicrosoft Dynamics IntegrationsMicrosoft Dynamics UpgradesMicrosoft Dynamics LicensingINDUSTRIESDistribution & Supply ChainFinancial ServicesPublic Sector / Non-ProfitProfessional Services
TRAININGMicrosoft Dynamics GPMicrosoft Dynamics CRMMicrosoft ForecasterMicrosoft FRxIT Security CompliancePassport Business SolutionsPARTNERS & AFFLIATIONSMicrosoftPassportESETSymantecMcAfeeFind Accounting SoftwareWorcester Chamber of CommerceCorridor 9 Area Chamber of CommerceWorcester Better Business Bureau
DSi BLOGABOUT USCONTACT USPRIVACY POLICYSITE MAP
While we are pleased to service clients from all over the US, our predominant customer base is here in New England.
© 2020 DATASOURCE INC..
All rights reserved. Powered by PDS eCMS Pro
